

CONTACT



+234 704 393 5291



ransomonwuka@gmail.com



Abuja, Nigeria



linkedin.com/in/onwukauchenna



https://ransom-data.netlify.app/

SKILLS

- Python
- Microsoft Power BI
- SOL
- Microsoft Excel

LANGUAGE

English

INTERESTS

Blockchain Technology |

Football | Data | Machine

Control and Automation | Data

Structures and Algorithm

ONWUKA RANSOM

SUMMARY

Hello. I'm here to consistently offer services to corporate organizations and businesses reputed for integrity, effective e-services, challenging work environment, career advancement opportunities. I have hands on experience and have used the data analytics technologies to analyze and proffer solutions to ensure growth and business profit optimization. I have a resilient problem-solving instinct which I have and will continue to improve by attending various seminars and bootcamps.

EXPERIENCE

ENUMERATOR

GeoPoll

Feb 2020 - Jan 2021

- Participated in qualitative and quantitative research. This includes collection of data from respondents through telephone interview, SMS surveys, Web interviews, face to face interviews, focus group discussions across diverse projects.
- Assisted in project implementation and communication project outcome with project manager.

DATA RECIPIENT

Co. Prime Global Insights

March 2021 - Feb 2022

- Carried out collection and compilation of data from different data sources and is analyzed which helps corporate businesses to understand the needs of their customers and how to solve the various needs. Most data sources where mostly offline sources.
- Worked along side data analyst and architect to assist in project launch.

EDUCATION

University of Nigeria, Nsukka 2015 - 2021 Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng), Agricultural and Bioresources Engineering with Second Class Upper Division.